#### Contact

matt.eckman@icloud.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ mattheweckman (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Computer Proficiency
Microsoft Word
Customer Service

## Languages

English

### Certifications

Dell Tech Direct Certification for Desktop Systems

Dell Tech Direct Certification for Printers

Dell Tech Direct Certification for Notebook Systems

Security Awareness

# Matt Eckman

IT Professional | Strategic Thinker | Process Improvement Innovator Alpharetta

# Summary

Upcoming Colorado State University graduate with a strong academic background in Business and Information Technology combined with experience in IT. Ability to quickly learn and master new technologies and systems with the skills for technical troubleshooting.

# Experience

Surgical Information Systems
Customer Success Analyst
November 2021 - April 2022 (6 months)

SweetWater Brewing Company Brewer August 2021 - November 2021 (4 months) Atlanta Metropolitan Area

Octane5 International LLC
4 years 1 month
Help Desk Team Lead
January 2019 - August 2021 (2 years 8 months)

Help Desk Specialist August 2017 - August 2021 (4 years 1 month) Alpharetta, Georgia

Atlanta Falcons
Desktop Support Technician
September 2015 - August 2017 (2 years)
Flowery Branch, GA

Provide support for desktops, laptops, mobile devices, printers, multifunction copiers and telephones. Using ZenDesk to process and complete a rage of high to low priority tickets per week. Also monitor multifunction copiers and

personal printer functionality in addition to provide general support to the IT department.

Georgia Gwinnett College Classroom Technology Support - Student Worker May 2015 - January 2016 (9 months) Lawrenceville, GA

Provided classroom technology support campus-wide in addition to assisting the Education Technology department. Classroom support entails doing campus room checks, checking and testing equipment (such as projectors and computers) and ensuring that they function properly. Working with Crestron systems and primarily Sony products, and respond to any classroom calls from professors that may experience difficult or dysfunctional equipment.

TruGreen LandCare Supervisor May 2012 - December 2014 (2 years 8 months) Norcross. GA

Maintained 12 commercial landscaping properties while supervising 5 employees and ensuring the proper policies and procedures were followed. I maintained equipment, provided customer service to clients and handled any complaints or concerns with clients properties.

## Education

General Assembly

Computer Software Engineering · (April 2022 - July 2022)

Colorado State University-Global Campus
Bachelor's degree, Management Information Systems, General

Georgia Gwinnett College
Bachelor of Science (B.S.), Business Management Information
Systems · (2015 - 2018)